Foot to the floor, we're cutting the wire
Leaving the city, feeling the fire
You wanted a spark, we're giving you flames.
We're done with the rules, we're done with the
games. Hey! Push it to the red line, never
looking back. Running off the rails, now
jumping off the track. Hold on tight, we're
losing control. This is the rhythm of a restless
soul.
The needle is shaking, tearing the street.
Burning the rubber, feeling the heat.
They're flashing the lights, they're sounding
the bell, but we're riding this rocket all the
way to hell.
Push it to the red line, never looking back
Running off the rails now, jumping off the track
Hold on tight, we're losing control This is the
rhythm of a restless soul
Faster! Faster! Tear the system down! Faster!
Faster! We run this town!
Push it to the red line, never looking back.
Running off the rails now, jumping off the
track. Hold on tight, we're losing control.
This is the rhythm of a restless soul.
Red line. Red line. Yeah.